Hello everyone, here to introduce to you the special effects of clothing transformation production method
Open a good clothing
First of all, select all the versions
Under the properties editor, open the selection of the seal
Note that you need to ensure that the selection is correct, otherwise the subsequent conversion will fail
Then open the UV editor, prepare the UV image
After completion, export the clothing as OBJ file
When exporting, select the object object according to the need
Select a single target, then hit
And select a unified UV coordinate option
If you need a larger and clearer picture size, you can set it to 2048 pixels
Select and save the text file together as one
Then click OK
More information about UV processing techniques and 3D format files can be found in our previous video
Click the Rearrange 2D location button below
Flatten the version
You can hide the sewing line for easy viewing
You can also adjust the layout of the version again according to the need
Then repeat the previous step
Then repeat the previous operation
Export the version to OBJ file
Open a new project file below
First import the OBJ file into the display tablet
Select the type of object, Avatar
The following two options are not selected
After importing, check under the high quality rendering mode
Then import the OBJ file to add clothing
Select Morph Target for the object type
Next, let's go to the animation mode
You can see that there is already a change animation below
Click Play to preview
You can also add a key frame to control the angle of rotation
Finally, there are two ways to export the video
One is to render it into an animation video or animation in the rendering window
The quality of rendering is higher
Or a faster way is to record the video directly
If you want to change the background later
You can change the color of the 3D background to green to make it easier to sketch
You can also set the background color you want
Here, you can record the video directly on the 3D window
Select the video capture animation
You can set the size of the video
After recording, save the video
You can also capture the rotating video of the costume
Do a combination display
Let's try it
Let me show you a performance in 3D
Once you've done, you can load the animation
To make it easier to edit the animation
For example, this is the animation in which the character is running
This is also an animation that is in the 3D render
In this animation, the animation was recorded without a 3D camera
You can also add a new animation
You can also add a new animation that is in the rendering window
You can also add an animation that is in the rendering window
You can also click on the animation to save the animation
For example, when you want to add an animation into the rendering window